bhojpurinama.com 2015-04-28

# Bhojpurinama - Privacy-Policy

### Privacy Policies

When you use the services of Bhojpurinama.com including uploading information about you that might be required by the website, it becomes necessary to be informed about the manner the information might be used by the website Bhojpurinama.com.

The world including the web world would know only as much as you want them to know about you. Your privacy therefore starts from you and depends upon the way you wish to protect the privacy . As a service provider we want to keep you informed about the ways in which you can protect your private personal information . It states following:

(i) What information we collect and use.

(ii) Why we collect some of the information.

(iii) What is the use of collecting and using your information.

(iv) How you can chose to limit and/or share the information with Bhojpurinama.

We collect the information such as your identifications, user name, age, sex, address, email ID etc. This is only in order to provide you a hassle free service and to keep the system free from any malware, virus. This would also help us keep in check illegal activities, if any, by any unscrupulous elements. We may thus also keep track of the system you use including the IP address of the system.

We also collect information such as language you use apart from the sites, programs or the posts frequented by you. This would help us serve you better. We would be able to know your taste and try to present tailor made things for you, just enough to suit your needs and keep you hooked on to the things of your taste. We shall always endeavour to improve your user experience and therefore such information may come handy to us for the same.

You may be given a unique number or ID by Bhojpurinama which would enable us to keep track of your activities, so that we are able to serve better not only to you but also to the other users of Bhojpurinama. We would however always endeavour to protect and respect your personal information as much as you do. Hence unless it is required by some fiat of law or courts we may not really share your personal details, just in case, you happen to share that with us.

Some advertisers may however wish to obtain your details to market themselves more effectively and to serve you as their most preferred consumers by offering the things of your choice. There are features in the website, through which you may block such sharing of information by us. Should you want us not to share those information we shall never disappoint you.

We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.

When you contact Bhojpurinama, we may keep a record of your communication to help us solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email ID to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements or some new products of your choice.

Respecting the privacy essentially involves limiting one.s entry to the other.s domain. But it depends upon you. Hence be cautious while creating your domain and your periphery.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Policy.

### Transparency, Choice and Privacy

As stated above, we respect your Private information and have therefore designed our services to suit to your needs. Hence there are features available in Bhojpurinama through which you can make such adjustments to suit to your specific concern related to privacy. You can thus review and control the information that you chose to share with us.

You may share and remove your content from the site. As you share we may use the information about you and the product that you share with us. We have provided different option for the purpose.

We may however control and keep a check upon your review requests should the same be a cause of concern for others privacy and safety.

Our Privacy Policy applies to us and not to others/other companies. Hence if there is a sharing of information by virtue of a system which is beyond our control, we shall not be held liable for such sharing of information provided by you with our site, by such a system.

We regularly review our Privacy Policy and its compliance. We also adhere to several laws, rules and regulations of the Government. We will not alter your rights or reduce it without your consent in that regard. We also have some self imposed regulations to serve you better within the four corners of law. Thus if we receive some formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint as well as the person/user against whom such complaint has been made. Such an interface would help us serve you better. 

We post such policy change on this page. So do keep visiting this page and enjoy your Bhojpurinama experience. We are there for you and your enjoyment. We are there to help you share your joy and experience with the world at large. Have fun!
